Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143
- UAW Solidarity, 1964-1965 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: UAW Solidarity, 1965; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.11 (1965: Nov.)
  - Item 21: UAW Solidarity, 1965; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.12 (1965: Dec.)
- UAW Solidarity, 1966-1967 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: UAW Solidarity, 1966; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (1966: Jan.)
  - Item 2: UAW Solidarity, 1966; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.2 (1966: Feb.)
  - Item 3: UAW Solidarity, 1966; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.4 (1966: Apr.)
  - Item 4: UAW Solidarity, 1966; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.5 (1966: May)
  - Item 5: UAW Solidarity, 1966; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.6 (1966: June)
  - Item 6: UAW Solidarity, 1966; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.7 (1966: July)
  - Item 7: UAW Solidarity, 1966; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.8 (1966: Aug.)
  - Item 8: UAW Solidarity, 1966; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.9 (1966: Sept.)
  - Item 9: UAW Solidarity, 1966; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.10 (1966: Oct.)
  - Item 10: UAW Solidarity, 1966; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.11 (1966: Nov.)
  - Item 11: UAW Solidarity, 1966; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.12 (1966: Dec.)
  - Item 12: UAW Solidarity, 1967; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.1 (1967: Jan.)
  - Item 13: UAW Solidarity, 1967; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.2 (1967: Feb.)
  - Item 14: UAW Solidarity, 1967; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.3 (1967: Mar.)
  - Item 15: UAW Solidarity, 1967; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.4 (1967: Apr.)
  - Item 16: UAW Solidarity, 1967; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.5 (1967: May)
  - Item 17: UAW Solidarity, 1967; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.6 (1967: June)
  - Item 18: UAW Solidarity, 1967; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.12 (1967: Dec.)
- UAW Solidarity, 1968-1970 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: UAW Solidarity, 1968; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.1 (1968: Jan.)
  - Item 2: UAW Solidarity, 1968; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.2 (1968: Feb.)
  - Item 3: UAW Solidarity, 1968; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.3 (1968: Mar.)
  - Item 4: UAW Solidarity, 1968; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.4 (1968: Apr.)
  - Item 5: UAW Solidarity, 1968; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.6 (1968: June)
  - Item 6: UAW Solidarity, 1968; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.7 (1968: July)
  - Item 7: UAW Solidarity, 1968; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.9 (1968: Sept.)
  - Item 8: UAW Solidarity, 1968; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.10 (1968: Oct.)
  - Item 9: UAW Solidarity, 1968; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.11 (1968: Nov.)
  - Item 10: UAW Solidarity, 1969; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.12:no.1 (1969: Jan.)
  - Item 11: UAW Solidarity, 1969; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.12:no.3 (1969: Mar.)
  - Item 12: UAW Solidarity, 1969; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.12:no.4 (1969: Apr.)
  - Item 13: UAW Solidarity, 1969; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.12:no.5 (1969: May)
  - Item 14: UAW Solidarity, 1969; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.12:no.7 (1969: June)
  - Item 15: UAW Solidarity, 1969; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.12:no.9 (1969: Sept.)
  - Item 16: UAW Solidarity, 1969; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.12:no.11 (1969: Nov.)
  - Item 17: UAW Solidarity, 1970; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.13:no.1 (1970: Jan.)
  - Item 18: UAW Solidarity, 1970; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.13:no.3 (1970: Mar.)
  - Item 19: UAW Solidarity, 1970; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.13:no.4 (1970: Apr.)
  - Item 20: UAW Solidarity, 1970; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.13:no.5 (1970: May)
  - Item 21: UAW Solidarity, 1970; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.13:no.8 (1970: Aug.)
  - Item 22: UAW Solidarity, 1970; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.13:no.10 (1970: Oct.)
- United Automobile Worker, 1940-1942 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: United Automobile Worker, 1940; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.26 (1940: Aug. 15)
  - Item 2: United Automobile Worker, 1940; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.27 (1940: Sept. 1)
  - Item 3: United Automobile Worker, 1940; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.28 (1940: Sept. 15)
  - Item 4: United Automobile Worker, 1940; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.29 (1940: Oct. 1)
  - Item 5: United Automobile Worker, 1940; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.30 (1940: Oct. 15)
  - Item 6: United Automobile Worker, 1940; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.31 (1940: Nov. 1)
  - Item 7: United Automobile Worker, 1940; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.32 (1940: Nov. 15)
  - Item 8: United Automobile Worker, 1940; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.33 (1940: Dec. 1)
  - Item 9: United Automobile Worker, 1940; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no.34 (1940: Dec. 15)
  - Item 10: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1941: Jan. 1)
  - Item 11: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1941: Jan. 15)
  - Item 12: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1941: Feb. 1)
  - Item 13: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1941: Feb. 15)
  - Item 14: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.5 (1941: Mar. 1)
  - Item 15: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.7 (1941: Apr. 1)
  - Item 16: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.8 (1941: Apr. 15)
  - Item 17: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.9 (1941: May 1)
  - Item 18: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.10 (1941: May 15)
  - Item 19: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.11 (1941: June 1)
  - Item 20: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.12 (1941: June 15)
  - Item 21: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.13 (1941: July 1)
  - Item 22: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.14 (1941: July 15)
  - Item 23: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.15 (1941: Aug. 1)
  - Item 24: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.16 (1941: Aug. 15)
  - Item 25: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.18 (1941: Sept. 15)
  - Item 26: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.19 (1941: Oct. 1)
  - Item 27: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.20 (1941: Oct. 15)
  - Item 28: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.21 (1941: Nov. 1)
  - Item 29: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.23 (1941: Dec. 1)
  - Item 30: United Automobile Worker, 1941; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no.24 (1941: Dec. 15)
  - Item 31: United Automobile Worker, 1942; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (1942: Jan. 1)
  - Item 32: United Automobile Worker, 1942; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (1942: Jan. 15)
  - Item 33: United Automobile Worker, 1942; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (1942: Feb. 1)
  - Item 34: United Automobile Worker, 1942; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (1942: Feb. 15)
  - Item 35: United Automobile Worker, 1942; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (1942: Feb. 15). Packard Local 190 Editions
  - Item 36: United Automobile Worker, 1942; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.5 (1942: Mar. 1)
  - Item 37: United Automobile Worker, 1942; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.6 (1942: Mar. 15)
  - Item 38: United Automobile Worker, 1942; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.7 (1942: Apr. 1)
  - Item 39: United Automobile Worker, 1942; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.9 (1942: May 1)
  - Item 40: United Automobile Worker, 1942; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.11 (1942: June 1)
- The Wage Earner, 1947-1949 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Wage Earner, 1947; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Author: Association of Catholic Trade Unionists (ACTU)
    Notes: v.9:no.48 (1947: Nov. 28)
  - Item 2: The Wage Earner, 1947; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.49 (1947: Dec. 5)
  - Item 3: The Wage Earner, 1947; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.50 (1947: Dec. 12)
  - Item 4: The Wage Earner, 1947; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.51 (1947: Dec. 19)
  - Item 5: The Wage Earner, 1947; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.52 (1947: Dec. 26)
  - Item 6: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.1 (1948: Jan. 2)
  - Item 7: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.2 (1948: Jan. 9)
  - Item 8: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.3 (1948: Jan. 16)
  - Item 9: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.4 (1948: Jan. 23)
  - Item 10: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.5 (1948: Jan. 30)
  - Item 11: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.6 (1948: Feb. 6)
  - Item 12: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.7 (1948: Feb. 13)
  - Item 13: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.8 (1948: Feb. 20)
  - Item 14: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.9 (1948: Feb. 27)
  - Item 15: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.10 (1948: Mar. 5)
  - Item 16: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.11 (1948: Mar. 12)
  - Item 17: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.12 (1948: Mar. 19)
  - Item 18: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.13 (1948: Mar. 26)
  - Item 19: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.14 (1948: Apr. 2)
  - Item 20: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.15 (1948: Apr. 9)
  - Item 21: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.16 (1948: Apr. 16)
  - Item 22: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.17 (1948: Apr. 23)
  - Item 23: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.18 (1948: Apr. 30)
  - Item 24: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.19 (1948: May 7)
  - Item 25: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.20 (1948: May 14)
  - Item 26: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.21 (1948: May 21)
  - Item 27: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.22 (1948: May 28)
  - Item 28: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.23 (1948: June 4)
  - Item 29: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.24 (1948: June 11)
  - Item 30: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.25 (1948: June 18)
  - Item 31: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.26 (1948: June 25)
  - Item 32: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.27 (1948: July 2)
  - Item 33: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.28 (1948: July 9)
  - Item 34: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.29 (1948: July 23)
  - Item 35: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.30 (1948: Aug. 6)
  - Item 36: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.31 (1948: Aug. 20)
  - Item 37: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.32 (1948: Sept. 3)
  - Item 38: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.33 (1948: Sept. 10)
  - Item 39: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.34 (1948: Sept. 17)
  - Item 40: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.35 (1948: Sept. 24)
  - Item 41: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.36 (1948: Oct. 1)
  - Item 42: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.37 (1948: Oct. 8)
  - Item 43: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.38 (1948: Oct. 15)
  - Item 44: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.39 (1948: Oct. 22)
  - Item 45: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.40 (1948: Oct. 29)
  - Item 46: The Wage Earner, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.41 (1948: Nov.)
  - Item 47: The Wage Earner, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.43 (1949: Jan.)
  - Item 48: The Wage Earner, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.44 (1949: Feb.)
  - Item 49: The Wage Earner, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.45 (1949: Mar.)
  - Item 50: The Wage Earner, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.46 (1949: Apr.)
  - Item 51: The Wage Earner, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.47 (1949: May)
  - Item 52: The Wage Earner, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.48 (1949: June)
  - Item 53: The Wage Earner, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.49 (1949: July)
  - Item 54: The Wage Earner, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.50 (1949: Aug.)
  - Item 55: The Wage Earner, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.10:no.51 (1949: Sept.)
- West Coast Sailors, 1948-1949 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Author: Sailors' Union of the Pacific
    Notes: v.10:no.34 (1948: Dec. 10)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.49 (1949: July 8)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.50 (1949: July 22)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.51 (1949: Aug. 5)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.52 (1949: Aug. 17)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.1 (1949: Aug. 26)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.2 (1949: Sept. 6)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.3 (1949: Sept. 23)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.4 (1949: Oct. 7)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.5 (1949: Oct. 21)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.6 (1949: Nov. 4)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.7 (1949: Nov. 18)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.8 (1949: Dec. 2)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.9 (1949: Dec. 16)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1949; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.10 (1949: Dec. 30)
- West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.1 (1950: Jan. 20)
  - Item 2: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.2 (1950: Jan. 27)
  - Item 3: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.3 (1950: Feb. 10)
  - Item 4: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.4 (1950: Feb. 24)
  - Item 5: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.5 (1950: Mar. 10)
  - Item 6: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.6 (1950: Mar. 24)
  - Item 7: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.7 (1950: Apr. 7)
  - Item 8: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.8 (1950: Apr. 21)
  - Item 9: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.9 (1950: May 5)
  - Item 10: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.10 (1950: May 19)
  - Item 11: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.11 (1950: June 2)
  - Item 12: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.12 (1950: June 16)
  - Item 13: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.13 (1950: July 7)
  - Item 14: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.14 (1950: July 21)
  - Item 15: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.15 (1950: Aug. 4)
  - Item 16: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.16 (1950: Aug. 18)
  - Item 17: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.17 (1950: Sept. 1)
  - Item 18: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.18 (1950: Sept. 15)
  - Item 19: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.19 (1950: Sept. 29)
  - Item 20: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.20 (1950: Oct. 18)
  - Item 21: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.21 (1950: Nov. 3)
  - Item 22: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.22 (1950: Nov. 17)
  - Item 23: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.23 (1950: Dec. 1)
  - Item 24: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.24 (1950: Dec. 15)
  - Item 25: West Coast Sailors, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12:no.25 (1950: Dec. 29)
- Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1906-1907 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1906; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Author: United Garment Workers of America
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (1906: Nov. 6)
  - Item 2: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1906; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (1906: Nov. 9)
  - Item 3: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1906; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (1906: Nov. 16)
  - Item 4: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1906; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (1906: Nov. 23)
  - Item 5: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1906; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.5 (1906: Nov. 30)
  - Item 6: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1906; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.6 (1906: Dec. 7)
  - Item 7: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1906; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.8 (1906: Dec. 21)
  - Item 8: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1906; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.9 (1906: Dec. 28)
  - Item 9: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.10 (1907: Jan. 4)
  - Item 10: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.11 (1907: Jan. 11)
  - Item 11: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.12 (1907: Jan. 18)
  - Item 12: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.13 (1907: Jan. 25)
  - Item 13: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.14 (1907: Feb. 1)
  - Item 14: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.15 (1907: Feb. 8)
  - Item 15: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.16 (1907: Feb. 15)
  - Item 16: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.17 (1907: Feb. 22)
  - Item 17: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.18 (1907: Mar. 1)
  - Item 18: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.19 (1907: Mar. 8)
  - Item 19: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.20 (1907: Mar. 15)
  - Item 20: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.21 (1907: Mar. 22)
  - Item 21: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.22 (1907: Mar. 29)
  - Item 22: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.23 (1907: Apr. 5)
  - Item 23: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.24 (1907: Apr. 12)
  - Item 24: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.25 (1907: Apr. 19)
  - Item 25: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.26 (1907: Apr. 26)
  - Item 26: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.27 (1907: May 3)
  - Item 27: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.28 (1907: May 10)
  - Item 28: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.29 (1907: May 17)
  - Item 29: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.30 (1907: May 24)
  - Item 30: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.31 (1907: May 31)
  - Item 31: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.32 (1907: June 7)
  - Item 32: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.33 (1907: June 14)
  - Item 33: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.34 (1907: June 21)
  - Item 34: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.35 (1907: June 28)
  - Item 35: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.36 (1907: July 5)
  - Item 36: Weekly Bulletin of Clothing Trade, 1907; Publication (Box 140, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.37 (1907: July 12)